whitehousedossier.com 2012-11-12

# Privacy Policy | The Blog on Obama: White House Dossier

**WHITE HOUSE DOSSIER PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last updated 26 May 2010**

White House Dossier (“White House Dossier” or “we”) takes privacy matters seriously. Please read below White House Dossier’s privacy practices (the “Policy”) to understand how it will treat personal information you provide online. White House Dossier may update this Policy periodically; any such changes will be noted in the revision date of the Policy. Any changes are effective upon posting; your continued use constitutes your acceptance of any such changes.

“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual and includes the following information: your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number(s).

White House Dossier may collect the following information, which may include Personal Information, through this website: (i) information you submit through this website and its contact form, and (ii) information provided automatically to White House Dossier’s web server.

This website is hosted in the United States by a third party service provider. If you access this website from any country other than the United States, you agree that you are transferring Personal Information into the United States. You also: agree to the collection, processing, transfer, and storage of Personal Information under US law, even if your local law affords you a greater level of privacy protection; and acknowledge Personal Information may be exported to third parties and provided to third party processors in compliance with US law.

White House Dossier may use Personal Information to: (i) send you materials or information you have requested, (ii) evaluate, update and/or improve this website; or (iii) to use your IP address (the number assigned to your computer while it is logged on to the Internet) to diagnose problems with the server or to administer the website.

White House Dossier respects the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. White House Dossier does not direct any of our content specifically at children less than 13 years of age. We will promptly delete any personal information we have collected about a user less than 13 years of age if we become aware that we have collected such information.

White House Dossier may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property. White House Dossier may also disclose your Personal Information in connection with services we obtain related to this website (such as data storage, hosting or other related services).

If White House Dossier transfers a portion or all our business or assets to another party (through merger, acquisition or another means), we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the acquiring party abide by the terms of this Policy.

For your convenience, White House Dossier may provide links to websites operated by third parties. We do not monitor the privacy practices of these linked websites and do not exercise authority over such websites. We therefore assume no responsibility for the privacy and data collection policies and procedures of linked websites, nor for the content or reliability of such websites. If you choose to access a third party website linked to our site, you do so at your own risk.

White House Dossier may employ cookies (a small data file which your browser stores on your hard drive). Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, most computers allow you to change your browser setting to prevent acceptance of cookies. By doing so, you may not be able to access or use this website.

To prevent unauthorized access, White House Dossier has put in place appropriate and reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure Personal Information under our control.

You may opt-out of receiving email from us at any time. Additionally, you may access, modify or delete your Personal Information you have submitted through this website. To do so, please contact us via the form on the contact page, which can be found at <http://www.whitehousedossier.com/contact/>.

If you have any questions about this Policy or White House Dossier’s privacy practices, please contact us via the form on the contact page, which can be found at <http://www.whitehousedossier.com/contact/>.

**WHITE HOUSE DOSSIER PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last updated 26 May 2010**

White House Dossier **** (“White House Dossier” or “we”) takes privacy matters seriously. Please read below White House Dossier’s privacy practices (the “Policy”) to understand how it will treat personal information you provide online. White House Dossier may update this Policy periodically; any such changes will be noted in the revision date of the Policy. Any changes are effective upon posting; your continued use constitutes your acceptance of any such changes.  
Definition of “Personal Information”  
“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual and includes the following information: your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number(s).    
Personal Information  
White House Dossier may collect the following information, which may include Personal Information, through this website: (i) information you submit through this website and its contact form, and (ii) information provided automatically to White House Dossier’s web server.

This website is hosted in the United States by a third party service provider. If you access this website from any country other than the United States, you agree that you are transferring Personal Information into the United States. You also: agree to the collection, processing, transfer, and storage of Personal Information under US law, even if your local law affords you a greater level of privacy protection; and acknowledge Personal Information may be exported to third parties and provided to third party processors in compliance with US law.   
Use of Personal Information  
White House Dossier may use Personal Information to: (i) send you materials or information you have requested, (ii) evaluate, update and/or improve this website; or (iii) to use your IP address (the number assigned to your computer while it is logged on to the Internet) to diagnose problems with the server or to administer the website.

White House Dossier respects the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. White House Dossier does not direct any of our content specifically at children less than 13 years of age.  We will promptly delete any personal information we have collected about a user less than 13 years of age if we become aware that we have collected such information.  
Disclosure or Transfer to Third Parties  
White House Dossier may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property.  White House Dossier may also disclose your Personal Information in connection with services we obtain related to this website (such as data storage, hosting or other related services).

If White House Dossier transfers a portion or all our business or assets to another party (through merger, acquisition or another means), we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the acquiring party abide by the terms of this Policy.  
Links to Third Party Websites  
For your convenience, White House Dossier may provide links to websites operated by third parties. We do not monitor the privacy practices of these linked websites and do not exercise authority over such websites. We therefore assume no responsibility for the privacy and data collection policies and procedures of linked websites, nor for the content or reliability of such websites. If you choose to access a third party website linked to our site, you do so at your own risk.  
Cookies  
White House Dossier may employ cookies (a small data file which your browser stores on your hard drive). Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, most computers allow you to change your browser setting to prevent acceptance of cookies. By doing so, you may not be able to access or use this website.  
Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, White House Dossier has put in place appropriate and reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure Personal Information under our control.    
Opting Out/Access  
You may opt-out of receiving email from us at any time. Additionally, you may access, modify or delete your Personal Information you have submitted through this website. To do so, please contact us via the form on the contact page, which can be found at http://www.whitehousedossier.com/contact/.   
  
If you have any questions about this Policy or White House Dossier’s privacy practices, please contact us via the form on the contact page, which can be found at http://www.whitehousedossier.com/contact/. ****
